搞什麼?
Aah!What the fuck?
這也太離譜了吧!
That was so fucked up, you guys.
前情提要
滾吧 你走人吧
Get out. You're done.
有一個人 你永遠無法打敗
There's one person you will never, ever defeat.
沒了我 祝你好運
Good luck without me.
我們企盼的解決方法
The answer to all our prayers.
一種殺死超人類的病毒
A virus that kills Supes.To make the virus
病毒強大到足以殺死祖國人
strong enough to kill Homelander would evolve it
就會演變成致命的東西
into something super lethal.
一場他媽的全球流行病
Global fucking pandemic.
我就是你 所以我告訴你你想這麼做時
I am you, which is why when I tell you you want to do this,
我是在實實在在地告訴你 你他媽的想這麼做
I am literally telling you that you fucking want to do this.
喜美子
Kimiko!
法蘭奇 病毒不會憑空出現 兄弟
Frenchie, that virus...it ain't gonna cook itself, brother.
我們不會拿萊恩當武器
We ain't turning Ryan into an asset.
他還沒準備好 要麼我們想辦法訓練他
He ain't ready.Either we figure out how to train him
要麼我們想辦法殺死他
or we figure out how to kill him.
停下來 快 停下來
Stop, stop! Just stop.
你的家人不是敵人
Your family isn't your enemy.
我媽不會希望我拍這個
My mom wouldn't want any of this.And that
這就是為何我對這孩子充滿信心
is why I got faith in the kid.
一旦他上任 我們需要援引第25條修正案
Once he's in office,we need to invoke the 25th amendment.
誰來處理這一切?我
Who's handling all this?Me.
我他媽的來處理
I fucking am.When Homelander
祖國人把星光追隨者們都關進拘留營
chucks all the Starlighters into internment camps,
你也覺得無所謂嗎?你對拘留營一無所知
you're cool with that?You didn't know about the camps.
你專心管好槍手就行了
You just focus on the shooter.
確保他六號那天準備就緒
Make sure he's good to go on the 6th.
你沒事吧?裏面熱得像個熔爐
Are you okay?It's like a furnace in there.
該死的變形超人類
Stop!Fucking Supe shapeshifters.
不過不得不稱讚智者
Got to hand it to Sage, though.
刺殺任務的完美人選
Perfect choice for the job.
沃特新聞網《今日新聞》
頭條 早上好 愛國者們
Good morning, patriots.
今天是一月六日 歡迎收看《今日新聞》
It's January 6, and this is VNN Today.
沃特工作室傳來令人震驚的消息
Stunning news out of Vought Studios,
沃特工作室緊急取消了 廣受期待的電影
who are canceling the eagerly anticipated film
《訓練火車頭》 雖然該片業已殺青
Training A-Train, though it's completely finished.
我們意識到該片的盈利前景慘淡
We just realized we'd make more from the write-off.
沃特新發佈了強有力的公共服務廣告 我們走進幕後 一探究竟
We go behind the scenes of a powerful new Vought PSA.
所有生命都重要 我承擔責任
I take responsibility.
我承擔責任
我承擔責任 承擔種族主義的責任
I take responsibility for racism.
最後一條消息 今天國會清點選票
Finally, Congress counts electoral votes today
對即將上任的總統進行核實
to certify the incoming president.
通常是走形式 但鑒於達科塔鮑勃極端的
Usually a formality, Dakota Bob's extreme anti-Supe agenda
反超人類目標 這次絕對不會走走形式而已
has made it anything but.
我們將以有序的方式清點選票 不經辯論
We will count the certificates in an orderly fashion,
議長卡爾霍恩清點選票
with no debate.
清楚了嗎?
Is that understood?
如我所說
Now, as I was saying,
核驗選票後
after ascertaining the certificates are authentic...
該死的病毒呢 法蘭奇?
Where's the fucking virus, Frenchie?
快準備好了
I'm close.
一旦他們敲響木槌
You know, once they bang that gavel,
紐曼他媽的就進橢圓形辦公室了
Neuman's one goddamn head pop away from the Oval Office.
還要多久?不大久了
How close?Close-ish.
操
Fuck.
是否有人反對清點阿拉巴馬州的選票?
...counting the certificate of the vote of the state of Alabama?
進入超人類事務局的數據庫了嗎?
Hearing none. The chair advises members of Congress...
我們得盡快查出那個變形者的身份!
沒有 我說過 維琪對數據庫把控得很嚴
No, I told you Vicky locked it all down.
還有 拜託你小點聲
Please lower your voice.
嘿 嘿
Hey.Hey.
嘿
Hey.
什麼事?
He-Hey. What...
你穿的是什麼呀?
What the hell are you wearing?
你不喜歡?
You don't like it?
不 我是說 我 我喜歡
No, I mean, I... I love it.
只是 時機對嗎?全國即將捲入
It's just, I-is now really the time, with the whole country
極權統治的洪流啊
barreling towards 1984?
我曾祖父出征前的那一晚
The night before my great-grandfather shipped out,
穿上了制服
he put on his dress uniform,
闖入我曾祖母家 在晚餐桌旁
barged into dinner at my great-grandmother's house,
單膝跪下
and got down on one knee.
好吧
Okay.
站起來好嗎?
Stand up. Please.
休伊坎貝爾
Hughie Campbell...
你願意娶我為妻嗎?
...will you marry me?
你站在這裏 好嗎?別動
You need to stay right here, okay?Just don't move.
好的 不要動
Okay.Do not move.
嘿
Hey.
我想我得跪下
Uh, I guess I'm-I'm doing this.
那我也跪下 求婚的是我 好吧
Okay, then me, too, 'cause I'm the one proposing.
安妮詹紐艾瑞
Annie January,
即將發生的事情令我恐懼
I am terrified of what's gonna happen.
但能
But I feel so...
和你一起面對這一切 我深感幸運
...so lucky...that I get to face it all with you.
好 好了
Okay, all right.
所以 總而言之
So, uh, yeah, all in all...
絕對同意 我們結婚吧
hard yes, let's get married.
英雄剋星
剛才 太爽了
Wow, that was... that was great.
兩根手指有點過火 但是
Two fingers was a lot, but...
對不起 我只是想更爽一點
Sorry, I was just trying to level up.
不 那是 沒關係的 很棒
Oh, no, it's... it's fine. It's great.
你要去哪兒?
Where you going?
我們得喝點香檳慶祝
We need some champs to... celebrate.
不能喝冰箱裏的柯克蘭廉價酒
And...not that Kirkland shit that's in the fridge.
我馬上就回來 好的
I'll be right back.Yeah, okay. Yeah.
議員們告知我 堪薩斯州的選票
The certificate from Kansas, the parliamentarians advised me,
是唯一出自該州
is the only certificate of vote from the state,
並附有權威機構認證的選票
and has annexed to it a certificate from an authority...
高壓90 低壓60
You're 90 over 60.
很低
That's low.
這還用你說嘛
You don't fucking say?
如果你需要任何幫助
You know, if you need any help...
我不需要你的幫助 真的嗎?
I don't need your help.Really?
在我看來 你已經 床上拉 床上尿了
Seems to me you are shitting in a bedpan
離入土不遠了
and days away from being planted.
你還有什麼牌?
And what do you have to show for it?
辛格爾?他玩完了
I mean, Singer... he's as good as dead.
祖國人 他贏了
Homelander... he won.
而你 你說出了病毒的事
And you... you gave away the virus.
唯一一件本可以阻止祖國人的武器
The one fucking weapon that could've stopped him.
但我們會扭轉局勢的
But we are gonna turn that frown
我的朋友
upside down, my friend.
知道為什麼嗎?
You know why?
因為你還有我
'Cause you still have me.
你他媽根本就不是真實存在的
You ain't even fucking real.
真是個很有趣的哲學問題
Well, now, that's an interesting philosophical question.
五號造成的腫瘤
See, what is real are the fucking
在你五臟六腑裏 大腦裏 雨後春筍般地生長著
V'd up tumors that are mushrooming inside your guts and noggin.
超級癌癥!
Super cancer.
你有時想要燒死
What is real is that piece of you
地球上每一個該死的超人類
that wants to burn every fucking Supe on Earth.
你覺得自己是怎麼 把以西結大卸八塊的?
How is it you think you ripped Ezekiel into fun-sized little chunks?
我就是那個賦予你所需力量的人
I'm the one that gave you the juice that you needed.
我可以再做一次
And I can do it again.
只要你履行諾言就行
All you have to do is hold up your end of the bargain.
要我付出什麼?
Bargain?
要我他媽的付出什麼?
What fucking bargain?
我們破釜沉舟
We go all the way.
毫不留情 拜託 哥們
I mean, come on, champ,
搞點種族滅絕算什麼呢?
what's a little genocide between friends?
滾吧 讓我安然離世 好嗎?
Just fuck off and let me die in peace, would you?
我倒是想
Wish I could.
既然你來了
Since you're here...
行行好 給我點酒喝 好嗎?
...be a doll and fetch us a pint, would you?
拜託 別這麼刻薄 我他媽的快死了
Come on, don't be a cunt. I'm fucking dying here.
我巴不得你快點死呢
Your dying's been pretty high on my wish list lately.
你來看我 我很感激
I appreciate what you're doing here for me.
我並不是為你而來
Not one bit of this is for you.
那好吧
All right, then.
把手機給我 我們還有工作要做
Give us me phone. We got work to do.
噁心
Disgusting.
該死的 萊恩
God damn it, Ryan.
過來
Come here.
過來 這是命令
Come here. That's an order.
我是你的父親
I'm your father.
他可不是
Not him.
我永遠都是
And I always will be.
馬上過來
Come here.Now.
萊恩
Ryan.
萊恩!
Ryan!
精瘦小伙子減肥午餐
嘿
Hey.
要是我就會小心些
You know,I'd be careful with those...
小心那些精瘦小伙子減肥午餐
...those Lean Lad Diet Lunches?
它們會害你長出大塊的腎結石
They cause kidney stones the size of jawbreakers.
這家公司被集體訴訟了呢
There's a whole class action lawsuit against them.
過來 不 別他媽碰我
Come here.Don't!Don't-don't fucking touch me.
冷靜點 好嗎?
Hey, chill, okay?
我需要補充面具能量而已
I just need a little recharge.
我他媽的為什麼要殺你媽呢?
Why the fuck would I kill your mother?
得去塞多納才能殺了她
That requires going to Sedona,
塞多納那種地方 誰都不該去
and no one should have to go to Sedona.
別讀取我的記憶
Get out of my head.
這個?
Oh, this?
今天早上我向休伊求婚了
I proposed to Hughie this morning.
我甚至還給他講了你曾祖父母的故事
I even told him the story about your great-grandparents.
然後我們就做愛慶祝
And then we fucked to celebrate.
我們肛交了一下下 他喜歡極了
And we did butt stuff.He was so into it.
天哪
Oh, Christ.
這裏熱得像個熔爐
It's like a fucking furnace in here.
為什麼?求婚多棒啊
Why?Don't you just love proposals?
對方臉上滿是喜悅
I mean, the joy on the other person's face
他們終於得到了永久的幸福快樂
when they finally get their happily ever after.
你個瘋子反社會者
You're a psychopath.Sociopath!
不難預料吧
Which is to be expected, really. I mean,
我幾乎不記得自己的樣子了
barely remember what I look like.
但我還記得自己的第一次變形
I do remember the first time I shifted, though.
我瞬間就變成了賈米森小姐的樣子
One minute I was me and the next I was Ms. Jamison,
她是我的幼兒園老師
my preschool teacher.
我可以看到她過往的每一段記憶
And I could see every memory she'd ever had.
跟她丈夫最好的朋友上床
Fucking her husband's best friend,
在商店裏偷唇彩 打學生
shoplifting lip gloss, hitting a student.
但你知道有趣的是什麼嗎?
But you know what the funny part is?
她覺得做這些爛事都是合理的
She felt justified in doing all those shitty things.
你們都是這樣
You all do it.
你們都認為自己做的事合情合理
You all think you're the heroes of your own story.
看看你
I mean, look at you.
比起我們這些骯髒下流的超人類 你更有道德
You're more moral and good and honest than the rest of us
更善良 也更誠實
just wallowing down in the shit.
我不這麼認為你就是這麼想的 拜託
I don't think that.Yeah, you do. Come on.
讀心術 記得嗎?
Mind reader, remember?
在選美比賽中
"Wasn't my fault
我是徹頭徹尾的混蛋 那並不是我的錯 是我媽的錯
that I was a total cunt at the pageants, that was Mommy.
必須像吸吮冰棒一樣給人口交
Or that I had to suck cock
才能留在超級七人隊裏也不是我的錯
like a fucking popsicle to stay in The Seven. No.
不
No, no, no, no, no.
我是安妮詹紐艾瑞 這不是我的錯
I'm Annie January and it's not my fault."
快點 現在就和我一起說
Come on, say it with me now.
我是安妮詹紐艾瑞 這不是我的
I'm Annie January and it's not my...
去你的
Fuck you!
對於我或我的生活 你一無所知
You don't know anything about me or my life.
是嗎?那為什麼你無法發動超能力呢?
No?Then why aren't your powers working?
最初甚至都沒選你 做殺死辛格爾的替罪羊
I mean,you weren't even the original choice to kill Singer,
但你麻煩纏身 一無是處
but you're just such a fucking hot mess,
選你再好不過了
you made it undeniable.
嘿
Hey.
你會被判好幾個無期徒刑
You'll have a couple of...non-consecutive life sentences
你可以好好解決自己的身份認同問題
to work through your identity issues.
求你了
Please...Aw.
可憐的安妮
Poor Annie.
求你了 天哪 我是安妮詹紐艾瑞
Please."Oh, God, I'm Annie January
我是唯一的好人
and I'm the only good one."
給
Oh. Here.
正好配那些精瘦小伙子午餐
To wash down those Lean Lad Lunches.
好啦
Okay.
休伊
我給你打了15通電話 我很擔心
Oi oi.I've called you, like,15 times. I was worried. I thought...
我不知道 還以為你
I don't know, I thought maybe you were...
是的 我也以為自己死了
Yeah, you and me both.
現在時間有點緊
Look, we're kind of up against it right now.
再過幾個小時 選舉的驗證結果就要出爐了
They're only a few hours away from certifying the election
之後 他們就會對辛格爾採取行動
and then, you know, after that happens they're-they're coming for Singer.
我們需要你的幫助
We need your help.
布徹爾?
Butcher?
年輕時
When I was a lad,
我聽說內華達州有個地方
I heard about this place in Nevada.
一家牛排館
A steakhouse.
女服務員給你上肋眼牛排時 上身一絲不掛
Where the birds get their baps out when they're bringing your ribeye.
好吧
Cool.
我告訴萊尼這事時 他笑得差點背過氣去
Lenny nearly pissed himself when I told him.
覺得是他聽說過的最好笑的事
Thought it was the funniest thing he ever heard.
我們本想找個時間去一趟
We was gonna go there someday.
說起來
Well...
將死之人想的事挺逗的 不是嗎?
Funny what you think about when your time's up, innit?
布徹爾 你在哪裏?我可以去找你
Butcher, where are you?I-I can come to you.
我們可以想出辦法來
You know, we can figure this out.
休伊 幫我們個忙 好嗎?
Do us a favor, would you, Hughie?
去那裏
Go there.
替我和萊尼去 好嗎?
For me and Len, would you?
你他媽的不能放棄
You can't fucking give up.
你仍然可以戰鬥
You can still fight.
休伊 我說出自己的請求了
Hughie, I asked you something.
好吧 我會 我會
Fine. I'll-I'll, um...
我會替你們去那家裸體牛排館
I'll go to the topless steakhouse for you.
感激不盡
Magic.
另外
And, uh...
告訴英雄剋星們我很抱歉 好嗎?
...tell the Boys I'm sorry, would you?
告訴英雄剋星們我很抱歉
Tell the Boys I'm sorry
因為
for, uh...
告訴他們我很抱歉就行了
Just tell them I'm sorry.
再見 休伊
Goodbye, Hughie.
對了
Oh, hey, um,
讓涅金給我買杯吉特咖啡店的 焦糖脆餅烤棉花糖冰沙
have Negin get me a caramel pretzel s'more frappe from Jitter Bean.
雙份起泡奶油 今天我又累又乏 沒什麼精神
Double whip. I'm just like molasses in winter today.
天哪 夠了 安布爾 謝謝
Ugh, God, that's enough, Amber. Thank you.
早上好
Good morning.
你今早還好 天哪
How are you doing this mor...Oh, God.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我們可以快點結束採訪嗎?
Can we just make this quick, please?
我今天還有稍微更重要些的事
I have slightly more important things to do today.
嘿 準備 等等 五 四
Yes ma'am, of course.Hey.Stand by. Going in five, four,
三
three...
祖國人和當選副總統紐曼 今天清點選票
Welcome to the show, folks.
歡迎各位收看 今天 我們給大家帶來了一個驚喜
We got a real happy surprise for y'all today.
祖國人和當選副總統
Homelander and vice president-elect
維多利亞紐曼!
Victoria Neuman.
非常感謝兩位來做嘉賓
Bless both your hearts for being here.
我很樂意為朋友祖國人擠出時間
I'm more than happy to find time for my friend Homelander.
閒話少敘
Yeah, let's cut the BS.
達科塔鮑勃說他會在上任
Dakota Bob says he's gonna pass nutbag anti-Supe laws
一百天內就通過 不合常理的《反超人類法》
in his first hundred days.
作為其副總統 您會如何阻止這種瘋狂的舉動?
As his VP...
作為超人類社群堅定的盟友
...staunch ally of the super-abled community,
我認為很重要的
I really think that it's important to...
盟友 維多利亞?真的嗎?
Ally, Victoria, really?
我們來做嘉賓是要說實話
We're here to tell the truth.
所以 說實話吧
So just... tell the truth.
事實是這樣的 真正的問題就是缺乏代表性
The truth is that the real issue here is lack of representation.
我們只是想確定 好吧 你不想說實話
And I want to make sure that you...Fine, you don't want to do it?
那我來說
I'll do it.
維多利亞是個超級英雄
Victoria here is a superhero.
謝謝你的稱讚
Thanks for the compliment.
但我認為事實是 我們都想成為英雄
But, like, I think the truth is we all want to be heroes,
可我實際上並不是個
but, um, I'm not literally a su...
糟了
Oh, fuck.
這都是真的
It's all true.
這位紐曼女士已然
Ms. Neuman here has been operating as
以秘密武器的身份 進入了暗深勢力集團
a secret dagger in the heart of the deep state,
勇敢地面對意圖褻瀆我國民主
standing up to the forces of darkness that want to
雞姦我國幼兒的黑暗勢力
sodomize our democracy and our toddlers,
但現在 偉大覺醒的時刻到了
but it is time for the great awakening.
團結一心 沃特力量 各位!
Where we go one, we go Vought, y'all.
我們稍後回來
We're gonna take a quick break...
秘密被說破了 不是嗎?
Cunt's out of the bag, innit?
現在有好戲看了
Now it gets interesting.
節目很棒 各位
All right. Great show, guys.
嘿 嘿!
Hey. Hey!
滾一邊去 嘿!
Ma'am...Fuck off! Hey.
我一輩子都在努力保守這個秘密!
I worked my whole life to keep that secret.
不過秘密會腐蝕你的靈魂
Well, secrets rot your soul.
你毫無負擔了 該感謝我才是 智者說
You're unburdened. You should thank me.Sage said...
去他媽的智者 她早被炒魷魚了 聽我說
Fuck Sage. She's long gone. Listen to me.
聽我說
Listen to me.
我們要改變世界
We are gonna change the world,
維琪 為了我們的下一代 以及他們的下一代
Vicky, for our kids and their kids.
第一位超人類總統
The first super-abled president.
而且你是個女孩子
Hmm?And you're a gal.
我會被彈劾
I'll be impeached.
我們為什麼要在乎?
Why would we care?Because I have to
因為四年後我必須再次當選誰說的?
get re-elected in four years.Says who?
《憲法》第二條說的新世界 新規則
Article II of the Constitution.New world, new rules.
現在 你他媽給我閉嘴 聽話
Now shut the fuck up and listen.
我們的命運現在已經聯繫在一起了
Our fates are connected now.
辛格爾已經完蛋了 你他媽的只有我這一個朋友了
Singer's as good as dead, and I am the only fucking friend you've got left.
覆水難收了 美人兒 這水就是你潑出去的
The train has left the station, gorgeous, and you're on it.
你必須得逮捕你公司一半的人 這個國家一半的人
You'll have to arrest half your company. Half the country.
怎麼 你以為我沒想到那一點嗎?我當然想到了
Wait, you think I didn't think of that?Of course I thought of that.
他媽的!
Fuck.
艾詩麗 跟我走 社交媒體上的反應不一
Ashley, on me now.Um, the response on socials has been mixed.
我需要你提交一份清單 列出公司內任何掌握
I need you to make a list of anyone within the company
對我或超級七人隊不利信息的人
that has damaging information on me or The Seven...
但主要是我 任何有談判籌碼的人
but mostly me...anyone with any fucking leverage whatsoever.
是馬上就交到我手裏
Yes.I need this fucking list yesterday.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
好姑娘
You're a good girl.
聽起來不太妙 艾詩麗 可不是嘛 艾詩麗
that doesn't sound good, Ashley.Oh, yeah, no shit, Ashley.
對不起 艾詩麗
Sorry, Ashley.
保持秩序!議長卡爾霍恩發言人結束會議
Order!
聯席會議的計劃已完成
The purpose of the joint session having concluded,
根據參議院 暨國會第一百一十八次會議 聯發的第一項決議
pursuant to Senate Concurrent Resolution 1, 118th congress,
議長宣佈聯席會議已表決
the chair declares the joint session resolved.
突發新聞 辛格爾及紐曼的選舉結果已被核驗
...certified the election despite the shocking news
選舉結果核驗完畢 儘管有令人震驚的消息稱 當選副總統維多利亞紐曼是超人類
that vice president-elect Victoria Neuman is super-abled.
全國各地均已爆發抗議活動
Protests have erupted all over the country
這下局面完全不同了
as Starlighters...That's the ballgame.
現在人人都有可能攻擊辛格爾 法蘭奇
Open season on Singer now. Frenchie, tell me you got something.
你最好是成功了沒有
You want to try this instead of me?
不然你來試試 我已經盡量加快速度了!
I'm working as fast as I can.
不夠快
Not fast enough.
多名抗議者受傷 至少十
Multiple protestors have been injured...
看到這條新聞了嗎?
You seeing this?
準備好紐曼的污點信息 防止事態惡化
Get all the dirt on Neuman ready in case we need to go nuclear.
等等 病毒研製得怎麼樣了?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. What happened to the virus?
沒研製出來
There is no fucking virus.
什麼?他媽的!
What?Fuck.
好吧 如果我們洩露這些 她會殺了我們 對嗎?
Okay, well, you know she's gonna kill us if we leak this, right?
相信我 如果另有選擇 我不會這麼做的
If I had another fucking choice, trust me, I'd take it.
管不了那麼多了
All right, here goes fucking nothing.
嘿
Hi.
不 他媽的!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Fuck!
怎麼了?發生了什麼?都不見了
What?What happened?It's all gone.
我們掌握的關於紐曼的所有信息 謀殺
Everything we have on Neuman... the murders,
她與艾德加的關係 等一下
her ties to Stan Edgar, everything.Okay, okay, wait a second.
你有備份嗎?另一台計算機 或者雲端儲存!
You got backups, right... another computer or the motherfucking cloud?
你沒仔細聽 信息不見了
You're not hearing me. It's all gone. The originals,
原件 備份 什麼都沒了!
the backups, we've got nothing.
那就沒法阻止她了
Ain't nothing stopping her then.
只有一個辦法了
Only one thing left to do.
法蘭奇 你留在這裏 再快點
Frenchie, you stay here, work fucking faster.
喜美子 你跟我走
Kimiko, you're with me.
我給你發坐標 你和安妮盡快去那裏跟我會合
Listen, Hughie, I'm sending you coordinates. You and Annie,
計劃是什麼?
meet there ASAP.What's the plan?
進攻是沒機會了 現在只能防守了
We fucked up our chance at offense. All we got now is defense.
對於這種對信任的根本性背叛
I am as shocked as you are
我跟你們一樣震驚
by this profound betrayal of trust.
在美國 要求別人給你投票之前
In America, you tell people who you are
要告知他們你的真實情況
before you ask for their vote.
正是因為這樣 我才呼籲新的自由 公正的選舉
That's why I'm calling for a new, free and fair election.
記住我的話
Mark my words,
除非我死了 否則 維多利亞紐曼
if Victoria Neuman becomes vice president,
絕不會成為副總統
it will be over my dead body
因為她派人暗殺我
because she had me assassinated.
我猜你得去 全天候保護辛格爾了 不是嗎?
Wow. Guess you got to go take a bullet for the geezer, don't you?
我認為我留在這裏更為重要
I think it's more important that I stay here.
你等的那個訪客到了
Your visitor's here.
讓他進來
Send him in.
夥計 這樣肯定不行的
Man, this is never gonna work.
你收到了我的短信
You got my text.
你來了 我很高興
I'm glad you came.
現在你已經快比我高了
You're almost taller than me now.
這孩子沒救了 遺傳的力量大得很
There's no saving the kid. He can't escape his own blood.
他們給你吃什麼?
What are they feeding you?
希望有點蔬菜
And tell me there's vegetables involved somewhere.
漢堡上有生菜
There's lettuce on the burgers.
我好想你 孩子
I've missed you, kiddo.
聽著 萊恩
Listen, Ryan,
我們得嚴肅地談談
we, uh, need to have a bit of a serious chin wag.
你看上去病得很重
You look... really sick.
可不是嘛
Don't I know it.
我巴不得自己痛痛快快地去了
Mate, I've wished myself dead more times than I can count.
可我還沒死
And now here I am,
我想要更多的時間
and I want some more time.
雖然我的時間不多了
But I don't have it,
我沒有時間慢慢地告訴你這件事
and I don't have time to ease you into this.
你必須殺了他 比利
You're gonna have to kill him, Billy.
你不能再回沃特塔了
You can't go back to the tower.
你需要和格蕾絲阿姨離開 什麼?
You need to go with Aunt Grace.What?
什麼時候?現在 馬上就走 不 不行
Like when?Now.Right now.No, I-I can't.
我爸會找到我的 這次不會的 孩子
My dad would find me.Not this time, kiddo.
可是
Well...
我不確定自己想離開
I'm not sure I want to leave.
我有點喜歡那裏 喜歡某一部分
I kind of like it there. Well, parts of it.
看到了吧?你得把病毒打入他的身體 今天就打
You see?You got to stab him with the virus and you got to do it today.
萊恩 不
Ryan, no.
你爸是一個 格蕾絲
Your Dad is a...Grace.
聽著
Look...
你媽去世不是你的錯 她離世時說的話
when your mom died... which weren't your fault...
你也聽到了
...you heard what she said.
她讓我承諾會保證你的安全 我正在兌現承諾
She had me promise to keep you safe, and that's all I'm trying to do here.
如果你告訴我 我是說 嚴肅地告訴我
Now, if you're telling me,I mean, seriously telling me,
和祖國人在一起讓你感覺最安全
that the place you feel safest is with Homelander...
那我不會阻止你
...then I ain't gonna stop you.
你想玩嗎?
Do you want to play?
那好吧 來吧
All right, then. Come on.
《靜水流深》 深海的詩
你見到萊恩了嗎?沒有
Have you seen Ryan?No, but I can send a PA
但如果你需要 我可以讓製片助理去找找看
to go look, if you need.No. No. Boys need their space.
不用了
男孩子需要自己的空間
清單呢?對不起
List?Oh, yeah. Um... Sorry.
先生 我用螢光筆標記出的人 跟我們簽了賠償合同 如果他們
Thank you.I highlighted anyone who's contract，we'd have to pay out if they're...
被辭退
...let go.
好 謝謝 做得好
Great. Thank you. Good job.
你去吧
You're excused.
沒問題 我能衝進去
You know, no problem. I can get it.
香菜口味
Cilantro.
先生們 超級七人隊的成員彼此信任
Gentlemen.The Seven is a circle of trust.
我們要告訴各位的信息極其敏感
What we're gonna tell you is extremely sensitive.
懂嗎?聽您指示 隊長
Got it?O Captain, my Captain.
這事一完 羅伯特辛格爾就得死
Robert Singer will be dead by end of business.
紐曼將宣誓就職
Neuman will be sworn in.
大眾會恐慌 將會發生騷亂
People will panic. There will be rioting,
流血 等等
bloodshed, et cetera, et cetera.
必須有人快速行動 恢復秩序
Someone will have to swoop in and restore order.
我們將號召每一位沃特英雄 每一位都
We will put out the call to every Vought hero,
他媽的包括在內 包圍國會大廈
every fucking one, to surround the Capitol,
白宮和五角大樓
the White House, and the Pentagon.
捍衛合法選舉出的總統紐曼
Defending the rightful President Neuman.
現在 我需要你們兩個
Now, what I need you two...
真他媽的 吃塊止咳糖
Fuck's sakes, get a Ricola.
對不起 先生 我非常抱歉 我只是 是服藥導致的 你知道吧
Sorry, sir. I'm-I'm so sorry. I'm just... the meds, you know.
你知道的 那種藥
You know, the... the meds.
會引發輕度心悸
They're just, they're causing a little
還有高燒 但這不是什麼大事
heart palpitation and a high fever, but it ain't no big thing.
你一咳嗽 飛沫濺得我滿身都是 真噁心
Okay, well, you're coughing all over me, and it's fucking disgusting.
往遠點坐可以嗎
Go further down.
挪一邊去
Scoot.
好的
再遠點
Further.
正如我所說
As I was saying...
今天 這份清單上的每個人都需要
...everyone on this list needs to be removed.
永遠地被清除掉
Permanently, by the end of the day.
如果考慮掌握我們污點信息的人
Hey, if we're thinking about who's got the most dirt on us,
艾詩麗不是應該首當其衝被清除嗎?
wouldn't Ashley's name be at the top of the list?
當然 好主意
Yeah. Sure. Good idea.
有人知道艾詩麗姓什麼嗎?
Does anybody know Ashley's last name?
怎麼
What the...?
公共工程部
你說變形者可以通過這扇門 不會吧
You seriously telling us the Shifter can get through that?
據我所知 他們可能已經潛入這裏了
Look, for all I fucking know, they could be in here already.
所以 從現在開始 每個人都要結伴行動
So, from now on, everybody moves with a partner,
每五分鐘準時檢查一次
and you check in every five minutes on the dot.
精神點 聽從命令
Stay sharp and follow motherfucking orders.
來吧 開始吧
Come on, let's get to it.
先生 您會沒事的
Sir, you're gonna be all right.
如果你們按照我的命令殺了紐曼
If you'd killed Neuman like I ordered,
我們就不會被困在地下四層
we wouldn't be stuck four stories underground
玩袖珍高爾夫球了 白癡
playing pocket pool, idiot.
該死
Balls.
喜美子 貼身保護辛格爾
Kimiko, stay on Singer.
你真的認為變形者在這裏嗎?
Do you really think the Shifter is in here?
我希望不會 看在上帝的份上 但變形者可以變成任何人
I hope not, for Christ's sake, but it could be anyone,
所以 留意所有人的舉動
so eyes on everyone.
沒問題
Okay. You got it.
天哪
Jesus.
你還好嗎?還好 我很好
You okay?Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
我只是 有點熱
I'm just... warm.
這裏熱得像個熔爐
It's like a furnace in here.
裏面熱得像個熔爐
It's like a furnace in there.
你去弄點水喝吧
Y-You should go find some water.
好 你想要一瓶嗎?
Yeah. Okay. Do you want one?
好啊
I would love one.
我馬上就回來 好的
I'll be right back.Okay.
他媽的
Holy fucking shit.
該死
Balls.
夥計 對不起 這事有點蠢
Hey. Hey, man. Hey, just... sorry. Just something... stupid.
不過很快就會說完 別面向我 面向房間
Real quick, just don't look at me, look right into the room.
別面向我 面向房間
Huh?Don't look at me, just look forward.
別面向我 面向房間 好吧
Don't look at me, just look forward.All right, all right, okay.
保持冷靜
Stay cool.
是安妮 什麼是安妮?
It's Annie.What's Annie?
變形者 是安妮 她是變形者 什麼?
The Shifter, it's Annie.What?
別面向我 面向房間
She's the Shifter. Don't look at me, just look forward.
你怎麼知道?
How do you know?
相信我就是了 我不知道變形是何時發生 如何發生的
Just trust me, I don't know how or when they switched, but that is
但那邊的肯定不是安妮 好吧 聽著
100% percent not Annie.Okay, okay, okay, listen.
國家的命運依賴於我們 保持冷靜 所以 冷靜
The fate of the country relies on us keeping our shit together, so just chill...
嘿!嘿!嘿!
Hey.Hey.Hey.
要水嗎?
Water?
謝謝 給你
Thanks.There you go.
很好
Yeah, great.Mm-hmm.
你看什麼呢?
What are you looking at?
我知道
Uh...I know.
你
Oh. Wow... you...
恭喜!謝謝
Congratulations.Thank you.
是的 我們結婚了
Yep. We did that.
我們做了那件事
That is a thing...
鄭重聲明 是我求的婚
that we did.For the record,
讓父權制見鬼去好了 對嗎?
I proposed. 'Cause peg the patriarchy, right?
對 讓父權制見鬼去好了 對 讓它見鬼
Yeah, peg the patriarchy. You got to peg it...
見所有的鬼
peg it in all its holes.
結婚 我一生中做過的最棒的決定
Listen, getting hitched,best decision I ever made in my life,
祝賀你們倆
so congratulations to you both.
但 你知道 我得去趟衛生間
But, uh, you know, Mother Nature's calling,
所以 我這就去衛生間
so I'm about to go hit the head, and...
你們堅守堡壘吧 可算中了!
y'all just hold down the fort...Yes, motherfucker.
天哪!先生 跟我來
Sir, get down.Sir, come with me.
先生 這邊走
Sir, this way.
完了
Oh, shit.
真他媽的!
Oh, goddamn it.
快走!
快!
Go.
快點!
Come on.
密碼怎麼這麼長?
How many fucking numbers are there?
天哪
Oh, God.
帶辛格爾走!快!快走!
Take Singer. Go.Now.
我們走!快!
Let's go.Go.
休伊 走
Hughie, go.
你真的認為自己 負傷後還能打得過我嗎?
You really think your broke-down ass can take me?
你連自己都解決不掉 不是嗎?
You couldn't even blast yourself out, could you?
你說得對
You're right.
我不知道我是否是英雄
I don't know if I'm a hero.
我他媽不知道自己是誰
I don't know who the fuck I am.
但我確實知道 我他媽的會好好教訓你
But I do know that I'm the bitch beating your ass.
維多利亞
Victoria.
辛格爾還活著 你的刺客失敗了「失敗」?
Singer's alive. Your assassin failed.
現在 中情局會更嚴密地保護他
What do you mean failed?Now the CIA's gonna find an even deeper hole to hide him in.
可新聞裏什麼都沒報道
Well, there's nothing on the news.
他會悄悄地回擊我
Because he's gonna hit me back quietly, and I'm fairly
我確信他有辦法做到這一點
fucking sure he has the means to do it.
智者在哪裏?
Where is Sage?
或許她能找到辦法 收拾你給我們搞的這堆爛攤子
Maybe she can find a way out of this idiotic mess you've dropped us in.
我們還沒有失敗 如果有必要的話 我會親自解決辛格爾
We have not failed. I will end Singer myself if I have to.
你將成為總統 然後 你要對我言聽計從
You will be president, and you will go along with every word I say
就好像我手裏 抓著每一條控制你的提線
as if my hand was jammed up your tight, puckered little asshole,
你要一直像木偶一樣受我擺佈
like the puppet you've always been.
維多利亞 如果你有一絲一毫的反抗舉動
And, Victoria, if you stray even an inch off that path,
我會確保佐伊餘生都活得生不如死
I will make sure Zoe knows nothing but pain for the rest of her life,
你的餘生里
and I will send you a piece of her every year
每年我都會寄給你她身體的某一部分
for the fucking rest of yours.
沒有什麼失敗!
There is no fail.
猜猜誰是強手中的強手
Well, guess who has two thumbs
他媽的天才中的天才?
and is the motherfucking genius of all fucking geniuses.
病毒制好
The virus is...
你們怎麼了?
What happened to you guys?
沒關係
你好呀
Hello, hello.
你還好嗎?
Um, you okay?
我很好
I'm great.
感謝上帝 你挺身而出
Thank God you showed up.
你是怎麼找到我們的?手機定位應用
How'd you find us, anyway?Find Your Phone.
我也找到了你的未婚妻
I actually also found your fiancee.Oh...
恭喜 不 她不是
Congratulations.No, she's not...
她不是我的未婚妻 不 你才是
She wasn't my fiancee.No, you're...
你把戒指戴在了她的手指上 休伊
You put the ring on her finger, Hughie.
我知道 因為她死後 我把它從手指上撬了下來!
Mm.I know because I pried it off her fucking dead hand!
我以為我要跟你訂婚 她的樣子跟你一模一樣
Look, I thought I was getting engaged to you, all right?
連那裏的雀斑都絲毫不差
She looked just like you, you know, right down to that freckle you have
所以 你確實幹了她
down...So you did fuck her.
我的意思是 你知道 多少次?
I...I mean, you know...How many times?
肯定少於
Had to be less than...
20次
...20.
天哪 我才離開了十天而已
Oh, my fucking God.I was gone for ten days.She almost
都是她主動的 再說一次 怎麼誇大這一點都不過分
always initiated, and, again, I cannot overstate this enough,
我以為是你來著
I thought it was you.
只要有人跟你上床 你才不會仔細看呢
Yeah, and as long as you were getting laid, you didn't look too close.
你想要的是那樣的安妮
That's the Annie you want.
什麼時候都肯給你口交 完美的女孩
Down to go down whenever. The perfect girl.
不是一個抑鬱的人 沒有歷經磨難
Not someone who is depressed or fucked-up
也沒有伴有任何並發癥
or comes with any complications.
你想知道我怎麼知道那不是你嗎?
You want to know how I knew it wasn't you?
在公寓裏 她穿著設計師款的禮服
In the apartment she wore some designer dress,
而你一到家就會脫下胸罩 換上運動衫
and you always ditch your bra for sweats as soon as you get home.
她一下子就找到了你的車鑰匙
She, she found your car keys
而你每次找車鑰匙都得找15分鐘以上
on the first try, and you have never, ever found your car keys in under 15 minutes.
但終極線索是什麼呢?
But the final clue:
在地堡裏 她滿頭大汗
in the bunker she was sweating,
而你總得裹著羊絨披肩
and you have always been and always will be 90% pashmina.
我愛你這一點
I love that about you.
你所有奇怪的 令人驚奇的反常行為 它們是你的獨特之處
All your weird, amazing fucked-up-ness, that's what makes you you.
安妮 求你了
Annie, please.
不
I can't.
他媽的
Fuck.
維琪?
Vicky?
我不想繼續下去了
I want out.
抱歉 這是 這是開玩笑嗎?
Sorry, is-is this a joke?
不是
No.
太過火了
It's gone too far.
你這麼說是因為刺殺失敗了
No. No, you're just saying that 'cause the assassination failed.
不 我這麼說是因為它永遠不會結束
No, I'm saying it 'cause it'll never fucking end.
祖國人完全失控了 甚至連智者的話也不聽了
Homelander's unhinged, he's not even listening to Sage anymore.
如果當上總統 我就會成為傀儡
If I become president, I'm just gonna be a puppet,
如果我反抗 他就會
and if I fight back, he'll...
我會自願辭職
I'll resign without a fight.
你需要讓中情局 停止對我的調查 幫我和佐伊離開
You just need to get the CIA off my ass and get me and Zoe out.
好吧 滾蛋吧
Okay, fuck all the way off.
你就像那個喊狼來了的混蛋
You're like the asshole who cried wolf.
你做過那麼多令人不齒的事
I mean, the shit that you have done...Oh, what?
像你們逼薩米爾造出更多病毒 殺死我那樣令人不齒嗎?
Like how you got Sameer to cook up some more of the virus to kill me?
還他媽的砍掉他的腿?
Oh, and, yeah, cut off his fucking leg!
很高興你們兩個聯繫上了 腿不是我砍的
Glad you two connected. Okay.So the leg thing wasn't me,
你並沒有留給我們什麼選擇的空間
and you didn't exactly leave us with a ton of options.
聽著 重點是 你攻擊我 我還擊 這種循環永遠不會結束
Look, the point is, you hit me, I hit you back,and it never fucking ends.
戰爭遊戲 休伊
WarGames, Hughie.
唯一的獲勝方法就是不玩
The only way to win is not to play.
我以為我想要從政
I thought I wanted this.
不是為了佐伊 也不是為了艾德加 而是為了我
Not for Zoe or...Edgar but for me.
你知道 我只是 我想要安全感
You know, I just... I wanted to feel safe, and not like
不再做紅河集體之家裏 那個被嚇破膽的孩子
that scared fucking kid at Red River.
但我沒有安全感 我真的很害怕
But I don't feel safe, and I'm really fucking scared.
我不要因此把佐伊害死
And I'm not getting Zoe killed over this.
這是唯一的辦法
This is the only way.
維琪 我不知道該不該相信你
Vicky, I don't know how to trust you.
我會告訴你佐伊在哪裏
I'll tell you where Zoe is.
她還好嗎?
Is she okay?
是的 但如果我去接她 就會引起太多的關注
Yeah, but if I get her, it'll draw too much attention.
這樣 你就知道自己可以信任我了
And that's how you know you can trust me,
因為我放心地把女兒托付給你
because I am trusting my daughter with you.
拜託 休伊
Please, Hughie.
你現在是全世界我唯一可以求助的人
You're literally the only person on Earth I can turn to right now.
別他媽的跑了
Enough fucking running.
對不起 兄弟 你在名單上
Sorry, bro, you're on the list.
別殺我 我可以付錢給你
Don't kill me. I can pay you.
你是個寫劇本的 你拿不到任何報酬 拜託
You're a writer.You don't get paid shit.Please...
要我做什麼都行
I-I'll do anything.
什麼都行?
Anything?
告訴我 我是超級七人隊裏 最聰明的超級英雄
Tell me I'm the smartest superhero in The Seven.
到目前為止 你是超級七人隊裏最聰明的超級英雄
You are, by far, the smartest superhero in The Seven.
你很聰明 是個天才
You're brilliant, a genius.
說你最尊重我 當然 除了祖國人之外
And that you respect me the most. Besides Homelander, of course.
當然 我當然尊重你
Of course. Of course I respect you.
你 你超凡脫俗
You-You're amazing.
你這麼說只是因為害怕
You're just saying that 'cause you're scared, aren't you?
不 不是的
No, I'm not.
我發誓你就是
I swear.Yeah, you are.
但你知道嗎 兄弟?
But you know what, bro?
對我來說 這已經足夠了
That's good enough for me.
你看到艾詩麗了嗎?
Yo, have you seen Ashley?
這就是艾詩麗
This is Ashley.
不 兄弟 另一個艾詩麗
No, bro.The other Ashley.
這個艾詩麗甚至都不在名單上
This Ashley's not even on the list.Well, I don't know.
那我就不知道了 這裏的每個人都他媽的叫艾詩麗
Everyone here's named fucking Ashley.
兄弟
Bro.
殺戮勃起
Murder boner.
你一定是在開玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.Look,
如果我們能策反紐曼 以她的強大超能力
if we can flip Neuman, as powerful as she is,
還有她掌握的沃特污點信息
with everything that she has on Vought, I mean,
哪怕只有百分之五的機會
if there's even a five percent chance.
怎麼 輕描淡寫地忘記 紐曼是個怪物?
Alors, what, just forget that Neuman is a monster?
我沒那麼說 我是說
I'm not saying that. I'm saying...
我們都幹過壞事
Look, we've all done bad shit.
如果她也像我們一樣 歷盡磨難 飽受痛苦
What if she's just fucked-up like the rest of us,
只是想為自己的孩子創造條件呢?
just trying to do right by her kid?
我們居然在討論這事 這已經很令人難以置信了
It's insane that we're even discussing this.
令人難以置信的是對於每個問題 我們的解決方案都是謀殺
What's insane is that our solution to every problem is murder.
以前一看到血 我就會害怕
I used to freak out whenever I saw blood.
現在 我連眼皮都不會眨一下
Now I barely blink at it.
不應該是這樣的 這不是什麼他媽的沃特電影
It shouldn't be that way.This isn't some fucking Vought movie.
暴力不是勇敢 恨我媽也不是
Violence isn't brave.Neither is hating my mom
恨火車頭 恨任何人都不是
or A-Train or...anyone.
但原諒 釋懷 懷有一絲憐憫之心
But forgiveness,letting go,a little fucking mercy...
那才是勇敢
that's brave.
這很瘋狂 但也很勇敢
It's crazy.But it's brave.
我爸教給我的最後一件事 我只是想
It's about the last thing my dad ever taught me, and I just think...
如果我們要戰勝怪物 就得開始展現出人性
...if we're ever gonna win against monsters,I think we need to start acting human.
那就做吧
Fuck it.
真的嗎?就「那就做」嗎?
Really?Just... fuck it?
安妮 我們可能橫豎都是死
Annie, we're probably dead either way.
還不如昂首挺胸地搏一次
Might as well go out with our heads held high.
所以 那就做吧
So...fuck it.Oh.
很好
Great.
聽著 嘗試策反火車頭?
Look,taking a chance with A-Train,
簡直瘋狂至極
that shit was crazy.
但看看結果如何
But look at how it turned out.
真他媽的
Shit.
那就做吧
Fuck it.
休伊 如果你錯了
Petit Hughie,if you're wrong...
信任 但要驗證
Trust but verify.
話說回來 法蘭奇 你能給紐曼注射病毒嗎?
But, Frenchie, can you get that virus into Neuman's system?
用帶有碳超材料尖端的飛鏢槍
With a carbon metamaterial tip to a dart gun
我會瞄準軟組織
and I aim for soft tissue...
也許吧 那就去吧
...perhaps.Then do it.
因為如果這是個陷阱 至少我們沒有盲目地跳進去
'Cause if this is a trap, at least we ain't walking in blind.
而且 休伊 如果紐曼有一絲一毫不對勁
And, Hughie, if Neuman even blinks funny,
弗蘭奇就會幹掉她 很公平 明白
Frenchie's dropping her.Fair. Got it.
聽著 我們需要 住口
Look, Annie...Shut up.
你要去檢查每一種已知的 人類會得的疾病
You are getting tested for every single disease known to mankind.
好嗎?
Okay?
我可不想被感染上梅毒
I'm not getting Shifter syphilis.
太他媽的好了 休伊!太他媽的好了!
Fuck yeah, Hughie. Fuck yeah.
你真的認為這樣做是明智的嗎?
You really think this is wise?
如果休伊是對的呢?
What if Hughie's right?
如果寬恕是 我們能做的最好的事情呢?
What if forgiveness is the best we can do?
連紐曼都能寬恕?
Even to Neuman?
寬恕紐曼
To Neuman.
也寬恕我們自己
To ourselves.
與我們相比 寬恕紐曼很容易 對吧?
Neuman is easy compared to us.
怎麼做?
How?
我想我們可以每天都做出一點嘗試
We try a little every day, I guess.
你記得我之前說 你應該和科林在一起嗎?
You know how I said you should be with Colin?
我撒了謊
I lied.
我只是覺得你值得
I just thought you deserved to be with someone...
跟比我好的人
Better than me.
在一起
Mon coeur...
沒有人
...there is no one...
比你更好
...better than you.
你們知道我能聽到
You know I can hear you.
「馬文說有人意圖 刺殺辛格爾
"Marvin said there was an attempt on Singer's life.
沒得手」我們知道 只是你不用擔心這些事 僅此而已
He survived."We know.There's just some things you don't got to worry about. That's all.
他們還會再次嘗試
They're gonna try again, and that virus
那種病毒是僅存的希望
is a Hail Mary at best.
我們沒時間了 也沒有更好的選擇
We are out of time and out of better options.
萊恩需要知道真相
Ryan needs to know the truth.
會告訴他的 什麼真相?
And we'll get there.What truth?
意圖暗殺總統 是你父親下的命令
The assassination attempt,it was on your father's orders.
什麼?
What?
還有37號航班
And Flight 37...
飛機上的每一個人都是祖國人殺死的
Homelander killed every soul on board.
格蕾絲
Grace.
你在說謊 我們有視頻為證
You're lying.We have it on video.
還有無數其他的人也慘遭他的毒手
And he's murdered countless more.
你父親並不是你想像的那樣 別說了
Your father isn't who you think he is.Just stop.
他並沒跟你媽發生婚外戀 格蕾絲!
And he wasn't having an affair with your mother.Grace.
他強姦了她!
He raped her.
對不起 孩子
I'm sorry, son.
然後呢?
And?
你的心在狂跳 你有事瞞著我
Your heart's pounding.There's something you're not telling me.
唯一能阻止他的人就是你
And you're the only one who can stop him.
阻止他?
S-Stop him?
你是說殺了他嗎?
Like, kill him?
不 我下不去手
No. No, I can't.
別讓我去
Don't ask me to.
萊恩 你很強大
Ryan, you're strong.
他更強大!我們會訓練你
He's stronger.We'll train you.
讓你做好準備 你們想讓我跟你們一起走 是為了這個目的嗎?
Get you ready.So this is why you want me to go with you?
這樣 你們就能教我 如何殺掉我生父?
So you can teach me how to kill my dad?
我得走了 留下來
I have to go.No, just stay.
我們會一起討論 我不想討論
We'll talk it out together.I don't want to talk.
我會回來的 我只是需要思考
I'll be back, I just need to think.
聽著 夥計 不會再有下次了
Listen, Ryan, there ain't gonna be another time for you and me.
我們暫時先冷靜下 好嗎?你不能離開
All right?Let's just take a breather. Yeah?You can't leave.
等等
Wait.
這些牆有近兩米厚
These walls are six feet thick.
這是中情局的黑茲萊特安全屋
This is the CIA's Hazlet safe house.
旨在關住你這樣的人
Designed to hold people like you.
我可以把我們封死在這裏 用氟烷充滿房間
I could seal us in here, flood the room with halothane.
我們都美美地睡個一睡不醒的覺
And we all take a nice, long nap.
但我不想那樣做 孩子 你們早有預謀
But I don't want to do that, kiddo.You planned this.
你們把我帶到這裏來是為了困住我
All along. You, you brought me here to trap me.
不 我們帶你來這裏是為了幫助你
No, no. We brought you here to help you.
除非我同意為你們殺人 否則 你們就會把我關在這裏!
You're locking me in a cage unless I agree to be your weapon.
就像他們對我父親那樣 事實並非如此 老實說
Just like they did to my dad.That ain't the way it is, honest.
讓我走 萊恩 失去孫子時
Let me go.Ryan.When I lost my grandkids, it left
我內心空空如也 喪失了全部的希望
this big empty black hole inside me.
可最偉大的奇跡出現了
Then the greatest miracle came along.
你
You.
我愛你 孩子
I love you, kiddo.
求你了
Please.
格蕾絲 我想離開
Aunt Grace... I want to leave.
對不起 別擋我的路
I'm sorry.Get out of my way.
格蕾絲 抱歉
Grace.I'm sorry.
不!
No!
什麼?
What?
我們進來了
Hello, hello.
上次見面後 你把牙套摘下來了
You took your braces off, since last time we saw you.
我們別搞這套
Let's not do that.Uh-huh.
紐曼 要怎麼做?
How's this gonna work, Neuman?
簡單
Simple.
你們幫我擺脫祖國人 還有辛格爾在中情局的人
You help me get clear of Homelander,and Singer's people at the CIA.
我悄無聲息地走人
And I go quietly.Mm.
你欠我們一份人情 不止一份人情
And you'll owe us one.A lot more than one.
我會欠你們很多人情
I will owe you many.
很好 所以 你會幫我們打倒沃特
Great. So you're gonna help us take down Vought
還有祖國人
and Homelander.
布徹爾?
Butcher?
沒有交易可做
No deals.
我可以解釋 好嗎?沒事的 我知道
I can explain, all right?It's all good. I know
這看起來是什麼樣 我們以前經歷過那麼多事
what this looks like, but with everything that we've been through together,
我從沒有要求過你相信我 這一次 我要你信任我
I've never once asked you to trust me. I am asking now.
就像你過去信任萊尼一樣
Like the way you used to trust Lenny.
拜託了 布徹爾
Please, Butcher.
住手!
Stop!
不
No, no, no, no.
別動!
Stop. Stop.
這是自殺
It's suicide.
病毒給我 謝謝 法蘭奇
I'll be taking that virus now, thanks, Frenchie.
絕對不行
Ain't no fucking way.
你注射了五號
You took V?
它也會幹掉你
It will work on you, too.
如果我是你們 就不會猶豫不決
If I were you lot,I wouldn't hang about.
順便說一句
Oh, by the way.
不用謝
You're all fucking welcome.
突發新聞 據報道 白宮處於封鎖狀態
We are interrupting our regular reporting with a breaking news story,
插播一條突發新聞
對不起 我只是
that at... I'm sorry, I'm just
在看製作人 已被證實了嗎?
looking to my producers here. Is this confirmed?
他們 他們告訴我消息已被證實
They're, they're, they're telling me it has been.
當選副總統 維多利亞紐曼去世了
The Vice President-Elect, Victoria Neuman, is dead.
全世界知曉她是超人類之後
Assassinated today only hours
才過了幾個小時 她就被暗殺了
after revealing to the world that she is super-abled...
萊恩在哪裏?
Where's Ryan?
畢竟這些都是為了他 對嗎?
This was all for him after all, right?
你來這裏做什麼?慶祝
What are you doing here?Celebrating.
我們贏了 給
We won. Here.
一切都毀了 計劃未能奏效
Everything's turned to shit.Plan's dead.
這就是計劃
This is the plan.
當然 略有偏差 但我們達成了目標
I mean, sure, a few curveballs,but, uh, we got here.
不能將計劃全盤托出而已
Just had to keep a few bits to myself.
讓你毀掉的那部分
You know, the bits you'd fuck up by...
你知道 你就是那種人嘛
...you know, being you.
紐曼本來就是個可憐蟲 固執 想法太多
Neuman would have been a shit patsy.Stubborn, too many ideas.
所以 我選擇了另一種方法
So I went another way.
鮑勃辛格本人下的暗殺令
...Bob Singer himself ordering the assassination.
如果你們按照我的命令殺了紐曼
If you'd killed Neuman like I ordered,
我們就不會被困在地下四層 玩袖珍高爾夫球了
we wouldn't be stuck four stories underground playing pocket pool.
現在 我們開始直播
And now we go live.
您看到的畫面是當選總統羅伯特辛格
Okay, that's President-Elect Robert Singer taken into custody by federal agents...
被聯邦特工拘留
She tried to kill me first.
在史無前例的事態轉變中
...in an unprecedented turn of events that is
那肯定是最為黑暗的日子之一
certain to go down as one of the darkest days...
找你的
It's for you.
是誰?卡爾霍恩眾議院議長
Who is it?Oh, Speaker of the House Calhoun.
一旦援引第25號修正案 他就是下一個總統候選人
Once they invoke the 25th,he's next in line to be president.
他想向你宣誓效忠
He'd like to pledge his allegiance to you.
向我?
To me?
就像我承諾的那樣
Just like I promised.
我們說好的
We had a deal.
是的 我破壞了協議
Yeah, well, I broke the deal.
我沒有
I didn't.
我告訴過你 你可以相信我 親愛的
I told you,you could trust me, boo.
我支持你
I got your back.
但我 把你趕了出去 就像 你是
I-I threw you out like...
垃圾
...like garbage.
你為什麼要這樣做?
Why would you do this?
看看我是否做得到
To see if I could.
謝謝
Thank you.
太有趣了
This was so much fun.
只是 你知道 下次
Just, you know, next time,
聽我的
listen to me.
下次?
Next time?
沒錯 金髮野心家!
Oh, hells yeah, blond ambition.
準備好 進入第二階段
Buckle up for phase two.
我是祖國人
Homelander speaking.
因此 作為我的第一項正式動議
And that is why, as my first official act,
根據《憲法》第九條第一款
under Article One, Section Nine of the Constitution,
我宣佈戒嚴
I'm declaring martial law
代表數百名全國範圍內的 超級英雄宣佈
and deputizing hundreds of superheroes nationwide,
他們將直接向祖國人匯報
who will report directly to Homelander himself.
以保持 謝謝您 總統先生
To keep...Thank you, Mr. President.
維多利亞紐曼 她是一個偉大的美國人
Victoria Neuman, she was a great American.
也是一位親愛的朋友
And a dear, dear friend.
被潛伏進我國政府的 暗黑勢力集團的星光追隨者
Murdered in cold blood by deep-state Starlighters
冷血謀殺了
embedded in our own government.
現在 我們擁有完全的合法權力
Now that we have full legal authority,
一支名副其實的 超級英雄軍隊將被召喚
a veritable army of superheroes will be called upon
把這些叛徒從我們的政府中 以及街道上趕出去
to rout these traitors from our government and from our streets.
美國將再度變得安全起來
America will be safe again.
對星光追隨者們說兩句 無論你們躲在哪裏
And to the Starlighters,whatever rock you're hiding under,
我們很快就會找到你們
we're coming for you.
我會找到你們
I'm coming for you.
因為今天
Because today...
超人類英雄的新時代開始了
...a new age of superheroes begins.
一覺醒來 我們的世界煥然一新
We wake up to a new world.
這裏充滿希望 純潔 耶穌的愛照耀著我們所有人
Where hope, purity and Jesus's love shine down upon us all.
孩子們可以在母親的懷抱中安然睡去
Where children can sleep peacefully in their mothers' arms,
因為他們知道 星光的戀童計劃已被挫敗
knowing Starlight's pedo agenda has been thwarted.
紅河集體之家
不好 不!
喜美子!
Kimiko!
在這裏 美國終於看到了 覺醒暴民的真面目
Where America finally sees the woke mob
他們是想要摧毀我們優良傳統的怪物
for what it is: monsters who want to destroy
拐賣我們的孩子 促使我國男性女性化的怪物
our heritage, traffic our children,and feminize our men.
在祖國人的領導下
Where, with Homelander's guidance...
我們將團結一致
...we will all come together in unity.
不!
No.
不!不!
No. No!
不!
No!
我們將使美國再次強大起來
We will make America strong again.
再次驕傲起來
Proud again.
最重要的是 超人類將再次駕馭美國
And most of all,we will make America super again.
你知道多久了?
How long have you known?
今天早上在機密報告會上才得知
Only since this morning's classified briefing.
我立即就聯繫了你
You were my first call.
向上帝發誓
Hand to God.
開什麼玩笑
You got to be fucking kidding me.
居然一直都在這裏?
This whole time.
獻給拉裏·克裏普克